Ri.  N.
Episode 4
Oh, Senpai!
There's the shrine!
Come on, Senpai...
Get the shrine, not me!
Oh, Senpai.
How was that, Megu?
I was embarrassed recording it, to be honest.
But I wanted to go on this date with Senpai!
Except it's not a date,
it's an extracurricular project.
Hey, wait up!
At least let me pretend, Megu!
We won't even get to go
on the same class trip, y'know?!
That's true.
Plus, Senpai's gonna graduate first!
Quit going into a downward
spiral over some homework!
Fine, then.
For today, you can think of
me as your senpai, Rin!
Senpai doesn't call me Rin!
I stepped in it...
I wish he would!
Don't cry, now. I'll buy you some dango.
I wanna eat them with Senpai!
How can you be so annoying
and cute at the same time...?
What is this? Did something happen?
We got into kind of a...
weird mood, I guess.
All right, who's the creep
who made you cry, Nanakura?!
It's you, Senpai...
Nanakura, club's over.
Still sleepy...
She sleeps like a little kid.
I'm hungry...
What do you want for dinner, Rin-chan?
Senpai...
That'll give you indigestion.
Y'know what, Senpai?
Stupid.
Stupid!
Is she really sleeping?
Oh, you're awake.
Senpai?
Nanakura, you were saying "I like
you Senpai" a bunch in your sleep.
I-Is that true?!
Playing Dumb
Stupid.
Here.
Oh, this is the thing they were talking
about on the internet. They say it's terrible.
Goya Drink
Yep. We found it the other day.
Did a little "Make it look like you're
enjoying it" contest and everybody lost.
I would love for you to give it a try, too.
I am kind of curious about the taste...
Huh. It's better than I expected.
Are you serious?! You drank
it like it was nothing.
What is this flavor?! It's disgusting!
Oh, that was acting just now!
Damn, actors can really
pull off some wild stuff.
I don't think I'd be
able to do another take.
I never wanna drink this again.
Oh, wait...
This would be an an indirect kiss!
Oh my, this is so embarrassing!
You have to drink the rest.
Don't try and pawn it off on me!
That's not it, honest!
I mean, come on, think of
the indirect kiss... y'know?
I-It's not like I w-w-want
to give you an indirect kiss!
Wait, what?
You mean Tsundere-chan drank some too?
This changes everything!
Not satisfied with it being indirect?
Imp-chan had some too?!
There sure is a lot left,
if that's the case.
Well, it is what it is.
Y'know, for actors...
You guys must be really bored
if you don't have any stage time.
They do say that waiting is part of the job.
Apple!
Shiritori, huh...
"Apple of my eye, I have to focus on my club
activities, instead of of being with you."
Nanakura. "You."
We're gonna play using only
romantic-sounding statements.
You... You...
"You're not supposed to spend time
with girls other than me."
That was scary! I got chills!
"Me? Are you sure I'm the one you want?"
That was just like a girl!
Maybe I should've let you have that one...
"Want..."
"Want me to look after you,
if you're not feeling well?"
That's kinda like a line a guy would say.
I'd like to hear it from you, someday.
I can look after you if—
I didn't mean right now!
Well, huh...
"Well, I like you, Nanakura."
M-M—
Me too! Me too! Me too me too me too!
Uh, you're supposed to
start with "you!" You!
You're good at winking.
I'm surprised you have
trouble with it, Nanakura.
Your mouth is open...
I really can't pull it off!
Maybe think of it as acting?
You're Imp-chan, and someone just caught
you skipping class in the nurse's office!
Don't tell anyone you saw me, okay?
Your mouth is way open.
Let me see yours again
for reference, please.
Like this.
This!
Don't stare too hard, now.
If you look too close... you'll fall for me.
Squee!
Oh, I hate this!
Nurse's Office
Pardon me.
I got hurt during P.E...
No one's around...
Senpai! Are you okay?!
Nurse!
No, I'm not...
I fell...
It's just a scrape, then.
I saw you go into the nurse's
office and... I thought...
You're here to finish me off?!
I am not!
The nurse does seem to be out, though.
Guess we'll have to handle it ourselves.
We've got all the tools, after all!
And... that is...?
What do you think?
You definitely look a little bit smarter.
Only a little?!
Here, let's get that disinfected.
You're gonna take care of it? Thanks!
You think it's gonna sting?
It looks so painful...
Nice and gentle please. I'm begging you.
Promise you won't get mad
even if it does hurt?
What is this?! I'm being healed!
That obviously isn't happening.
I bet a demure nurse would be very gentle...
You're a big boy, so you
can hang in there, right?
Hell yeah! Hit me with it!
That doesn't sting at all.
There. All done.
Thank you.
Sure.
Oh, and I'm actually hurt here, too..
Nurse? You're bright red.
That is not true!
You might need an eye exam!
Let's begin.
Ni
What does this say?
Tsu.
Ni                          Ha
N. De. Re.
Ri                 Sa               Na
You just wanted to say tsundere...
I do feel like my eyesight's
gotten worse, though.
Tsundere-chan, what kind of glasses
do you think I'd look good in?
How should I know?!
Why are you even asking me?!
Well, you seem the most likely
to give me a serious answer...
If I have to...
I can't even look at you directly!
You've really mastered those things.
Come on, let's do this seriously!
Ku                                  N
Ri                 Sa                 Na
I                  Ku                  To
Na. Na. Ku. Ra.
To                      Ma                      Ra
What happened to taking it seriously?
And that was a guess at the end there.
I couldn't actually read that "Ra."
In that case...
Ri                 Sa                Na
Ri N... Ri N...
Rin-chan?!
Ri.. N...
You literally just did it again, didn't you?
Pseudo Harem
Pseudo
Harem
This was
a bad
idea!
Nanakura.
Yes?
That new dungeon is too tough for me.
Wanna do co-op?
Sure! Let's do it!
What kinda team comp should we use?
I guess I'll focus on debuffs.
Curse-style, huh?
That sounds like a team Imp-chan would use.
But you're the one who bewitched me, Senpai.
I-I might get distracted, so...
Be ready to rez me, okay?
Not good!
This dungeon is too tough to
beat without taking it seriously!
Wow, Nanakura, you're pretty hardcore.
I wanted to play with you, Senpai.
I can't focus at all!
Aw— What—
I'm sorry...
I didn't think you'd be that distracted.
Again!
This time we're gonna
beat it so I can go home!
Then why don't you show me your moves?
Please stop acting, Nanakura!
Can you see your house from here, Senpai?
Yeah. Just barely.
How about yours?
It's over there. But you
can't see it at all...
I'd like to go to Senpai's house again.
I bet Tsundere-chan lives in
that high-rise apartment building.
She's rich?!
She's a tsundere, so naturally.
I wonder where Cool-chan lives?
Maybe over there?
Looks like she's from
a distinguished family!
A real princess.
What kind of house would
you like to live in?
Let's see...
- The one with the blue roof—
Oh, wow! We picked the same place.
Then again, I was first, so...
It was at the same time!
Maybe... we could live there together...?
- Dibs on the second floor—
Same room too, huh...?
Something about rain gets me hyped!
I hate it when my socks get soaked!
I realize this isn't a great time, but...
Wouldn't it be super cute if
Cool-chan was scared of thunder?
What are you talking about?
I'm not really scared.
What're you doing?
You don't have to go that far.
You put the idea in my head.
Then just ignore my nonsense!
But I can't deny that I'd like
to see Imp-chan acting scared!
Protect me for now, okay?
Don't play with your umbrella!
That one was kinda close, huh.
I'm scared...!
You wanna hang out at my
place until the rain lets up?
Yes!
Are you... actually scared or...?
Sure am!
Pardon the intrusion.
Man, we're soaked.
We sure are.
You want a change of clothes?
That way your uniform can dry.
Not only am I at his house,
I'm wearing his clothes!
We're basically dating
at this point, right?!
When you're done changing,
you can hang out in my room.
Or the living room, if you like.
I'll go to your room!
Senpai's room...
It's Senpai's room!
His room, his room, his room, his room!
Nanakura!
When my mom gets home,
she's gonna insist on you eating with us.
Is it okay if you're
late heading home today?
Wearing matching outfits...
And meeting his parents?!
I think I'll change back into my uniform!
Uh, it's definitely not dry yet!
B-But...!
I'm home.
Hey, there she is.
But... but this is... wow!
Have we got company?
I-It's nice to meet you.
My name is Nanakura Rin.
This is my kouhai from Drama.
She's waiting out the rain.
Wow!
Thank you for the meal.
It was very good.
Be careful on your way home.
Right. Thanks for having me.
Come visit again, Rin-chan!
S-Sure!
I wish I could've stayed longer...
You really hit it off with Mom!
She was calling you Rin-chan and everything.
Nanakura?
I want you to call me Rin, too, Senpai.
You can come by whenever you want... Rin.
Man, this is really embarrassing!
You're actually blushing, Senpai!
So are you, Nanakura!
Rin! It's Rin!
Fine, Rin Nanakura.
That's how a foreigner would say it!
Rin Nanakura?
Much Ado About Nothing
Oh, you're too much! Much...
Much Ado About Nothing!
I've got an idea for
the place I'd like to live.
It'd have a really comfortable living room,
with a lot of space,
warm decor, and a big window...
That sounds girly, all right.
A house where the married couple can relax
and the children can be lively!
I guess this backdrop won't cut it then?
Obviously not.